A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Secretary of Public Safety, 1990; 1992; 1996; 1998-2010 (bulk 2002-2009)
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Assigned State Agencies, 1996; 1999-2010., Extent: 11.0 cu. ft. (11 boxes) (Box 1-11)
  - Forensic Science, Department of
    - Lab Review, 2005-2007. (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk Laboratory/Ballard Property, 2007. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Replacement of Northern Virginia Forensic Laboratory, 2005. (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Northern Forensic Laboratory Groundbreaking, 2007. (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Scientific Advisory Committee, 2008. (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Transition Activities, 2005. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Juvenile Justice, Department of
    - Agency Overview, 2001. (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Audit Report, 2007-2008. (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Culpeper Juvenile Correctional Center, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Culpeper Juvenile Correctional Center, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Culpeper Juvenile Correctional Center, 2002. (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Data Resource Guide, Fiscal Year 2001, December 2001. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Data Resource Guide, Fiscal Year 2002, December 2002. (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Data Resource Guide, Fiscal Year 2002, December 2002 (copy 2). (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Data Resource Guide, Fiscal Year 2003, December 2003. (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Data Resource Guide, Fiscal Year 2005, December 2005. (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Data Resource Guide, Fiscal Year 2007, December 2007. (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Offices on Youth/DJJ Regulations, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Regulations, 2001-2002. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Report: House Appropriations Committee, Public Safety Sub-Committee, 23 January 2002. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Report: Restructuring Proposal for Juvenile Correctional Centers, 14 March 2002. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Reports and Presentations, 2004, 2006 and undated. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Department of Juvenile Justice, Workforce Plans, 2006-2008. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - United States Department of Justice, Miscellaneous Reports, 2006-2007. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Military Affairs, Department of
    - News articles about the 203d Red Horse Flight Fatalities, 2001. (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Camp Pendleton Facility, 2002-2004. (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Department of Military Affairs, Command Briefing for Chief of Staff Wayne Turnage, 4 June 2007. (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Commission on the National Guard and Reserves, Second Report to Congress, 1 March 2007. (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Commission on the National Guard and Reserves, Final Report to Congress and the Secretary of Defense, 31 January 2008. (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Determined Promise Defense Exercise (DP-04), 2004. (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Driver Training Facility/Fort Pickett, 2004. (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Fort Lee Land, 2002-2005. (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence, 2003-2004. (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Laws, 2004. (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Reports, 2005-2006, 2008. (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Virginia National Guard, undated. (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Parole Board
    - Appointments, 2001-2002. (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Department of Corrections and Virginia Parole Board, 30 June 2006. (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - General Correspondence, 2002-2004. (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence, 2008-2009. (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Laws, 2002. (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Monthly Decision Lists, 2000-2001. (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Statistical Report, 2001. (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Virginia State Police
    - Asset Forfeiture Program, 2002-2007. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Asset Forfeiture Program, 2009. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts, Department of State Police Reports, 2005, 2007-2008. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Bias-Based Policing (part 1), 2001-2002. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Bias-Based Policing (part 2), 2001-2003. (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Bias-Based Policing (part 3), 2001-2003. (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Budget, 2007-2009. (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Civil Forfeiture Settlement, 6 April 2007. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Compensation and Retention Plan, 2002-2003, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Crime in Virginia, 2003, written by Uniform Crime Reporting Section, Department of State Police, 2003. (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Dulles Toll Road, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2002-2005. (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - General Correspondence, 2009-2010. (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - HOV Committee/Northern Virginia, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Immigration Customs Enforcement (ICE), 2006-2008. (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Insurance Fraud Program Annual Reports, 2005-2007. (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Interoperability, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Law Enforcement Activity Management System, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Manpower Augmentation Study, 2005-2006. (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Minority Recruiting Efforts, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Operation Air, Land and Speed, 2007. (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Operations Manual, Newport News Shipbuilding Strike, 2004. (Box 9, Folder 31)
    - Primary Safety Belt Legislation, 2006. (Box 9, Folder 32)
    - Washington Regional Alcohol Program, 2002 Virginia Checkpoint Strikeforce Campaign, Final Report, 31 March 2003. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous Reports and Applications, 2003, 2007. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Reports and Studies, 1996, 2001-2002. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 2005-2008. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Progress Reports, Uniform Accident Prevention Program, State Owned Vehicles, 2001-2005. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Secretary of Public Safety Security Alert Plan, 2003. (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2003. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2004. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2004. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2006. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2007. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2008. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), 2009. (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2007. (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2007. (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2008. (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2008. (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2009. (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2009. (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Statewide Agencies Radio System (STARS), Monthly Reports, 2009. (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Statewide Driver Training Facility, ca. 2002. (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Statistical Summaries of Narcotics Enforcement, 2005. (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Statistical Summaries of Narcotics Enforcement, 2006. (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Statistical Summaries of Narcotics Enforcement, 2007. (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Statistical Summaries of Narcotics Enforcement, 2008. (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Statistical Summaries of Narcotics Enforcement, 2009. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Youth Internet Safety Task Force, 2006-2007. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - VITA Concerns, 2006-2007. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Veterans Services, Department of
    - Audit, 2006-2008. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Best Practices Team, 2004. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Budget, 2005. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Executive Order 19, Serving Virginia's Veterans, Report to Governor Timothy M. Kaine, 30 April 2007 (Draft). (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - General Assembly (2005 session), 2004-2005. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2007. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2008. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2009. (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Itinerant Service Update, 2005. (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Patient Billing Software, 2006. (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Reports, 2007-2008. (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Veterans Workforce Development Taskforce (VWDT), 2006-2008. (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, 1990; 1992; 1998-2009., Extent: 19.4 cubic feet (22 boxes). (Box 12-30)
  The Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary series is housed in 22 boxes and is arranged into five subseries. Subseries have been designated for: A. Correspondence Files, B. Subject Files, C. Records of Deputy Secretary Barry Green, D. Records of Deputy Secretary Dawn Smith; and E. Records of Assistant Secretary/Deputy Secretary Marilyn Harris.
  - Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, Subseries A. Correspondence, 2002-2009., Extent: 3.0 cu. ft. (boxes 12-14)
    This subseries is housed in three boxes and is arranged alphabetically by first letter of last name and by date therein. It documents the incoming and outgoing correspondence to the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety and covers the tenure of Secretary John Marshall from 2002 to 2010. Included are constituent correspondence and general correspondence.
    - Constituent Correspondence (Not Scanned into IQ), 2006-2009. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - A, 2008-2009. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - A, 2002-2007. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - B, 2009. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - B, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - B, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - B, 2004-2006. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - C, 2009. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - C, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - C, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - C, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - C, 2002-2006. (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - D, 2008-2009. (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - D, 2007. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - D, 2002-2006. (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - E, 2006-2009. (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - F, 2008-2009. (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - F, 2002-2007. (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - G, 2008-2009. (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - G, 2006-2007. (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - H, 2009. (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - H, 2008. (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - H, 2007. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - H, 2002-2006. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Hersch, Jay (Highland Beef), 2007. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Huff, Delby, 2006-2009. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - I, 2006-2008. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - J, 2007-2009. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - J, 2002-2006. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Johnson, Clyde, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - K, 2008-2009. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - K, 2006-2007. (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - L, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - L, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - L, 2006-2007. (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - M, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - M, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - M, 2007. (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - M, 2006. (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Mc, 2006-2009. (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - N, 2005-2009. (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - O, 2004-2009. (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Omar, Shaheed, 2004-2006. (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Omar, Shaheed, 2004-2006. (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - P, 2008-2009. (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - P, 2007. (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - P, 2006. (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Parker, Stephen, 2009. (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Plakash, Ed, 2008. (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - R, 2009. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - R, 2008. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - R, 2007. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - R, 2006. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Rhinehults, Gary, 2007-2008. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Rychlik, Kevin, 2009. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - S, 2009. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - S, 2008. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - S, 2007. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - S, 2006. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - S, 2002-2006. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Singh, Prakash, 2009. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - T, 2008-2009. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - T, 2007. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - T, 2002-2006. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - U, 2006; 2009. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - V, 2008-2009. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - V, 2007. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - V, 2002-2006. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - W, 2009. (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - W, 2008. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - W, 2007. (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - W, 2006. (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Y, 2006. (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Z, 2006-2009. (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Series II. Correspondence and Supporting Documentation - Office of the Secretary, Subseries B. Subject Files, 1990; 1992; 2001-2009., Extent: 9.05 cu. ft. (boxes 15-22c)
    This subseries is housed in 11 boxes and documents the subject files of the Office of the Secretary of Public Safety and covers the tenure of Secretary John Marshall from 2002 to 2010. Included are lists of Secretary of Public Safety accomplishments for 2002, 2004, 2007 and 2008; disaster designation letters and update; Forensic/DNA notification process; gubernatorial incapacity and succession; Homeland Security; Inmate telephone system; Hurricane Katrina; Medal of Valor award; and Public Safety agency head meetings (2002-2008). The files arranged alphabetically by subject.
    - ABC Equity Pay Proposal, 2005. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Accomplishments, 2007. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Accomplishments, 2008-2009. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Accomplishments, undated. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Accomplishments, Issues and Opportunities, 2002-2004. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Dispute Resolution, 2006-2009. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Agency Budget Reduction Plans (2008-2010), 2008. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Agency Citizen's Communications, 2006-2007. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Agency Head and Legislative Liaison Meeting, 2006. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Agency Water Conservation, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Aid to Localities with Police Departments (599 Funds), 2006. (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Amber Alert, 2006. (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Anonymous Letters, 2002; undated. (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Appointment Calendars, 2006-2007. (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Appointments - Agency Heads, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Appointments - Agency Heads, 2003-2004. (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Appointments - Agency Heads, 2005. (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - Appointments - Agency Heads, 2006. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Appointments - Agency Heads, 2009. (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - "Ask Why" Program, 2002-2003. (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - "Ask Why" Program, 2002. (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - At-Will Employees, 2007. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - At-Will Pay Increases, 2002-2007. (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Attorney General Opinions, 2002-2009. (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts Reports, 2002-2005. (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts Reports, 2006. (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts Reports, 2007-2009. (Box 22a, Folder 1)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts Reports, 2006-2007. (Box 22a, Folder 2)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts Reports, 2006-2008. (Box 22a, Folder 3)
    - Auditor of Public Accounts Report, 2009. (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Bias-Based Policing: A Study of The Commonwealth of Virginia, 30 August 2004. (Box 15, Folder 27a)
    - Board Appointments, 2009. (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Board Profiles, 2006. (Box 15, Folder 29)
    - Board Profiles, 2007. (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Board Profiles, 2008. (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Brain Injuries, 2006-2007. (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Budget, 2005. (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Budget Request Brief for the 2004-2006 Biennium, Alcoholic Beverage Control-Corrections, ca. October 2003. (Box 22a, Folder 4)
    - Budget Request Brief for the 2004-2006 Biennium, Criminal Justice Services-Fire Programs, ca. October 2003. (Box 22a, Folder 5)
    - Budget Request Brief for the 2004-2006 Biennium, Juvenile Justice-State Police, ca. October 2003. (Box 22a, Folder 6)
    - Budget Reports, 17 February 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 7)
    - Cabinet Meetings, 2003-2006. (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Cabinet Schedule Requests for Governor Kaine to Attend Events, 2006. (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Cabinet Schedule Requests for Governor Kaine to Attend Events, 2007. (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Cabinet Schedule Requests for Governor Kaine to Attend Events, 2008. (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Cabinet Schedule Requests for Governor Kaine to Attend Events, 2009. (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Cabinet Schedule Requests for the First Lady to Attend Events, 2006-2009. (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Capital Outlay Progress reports, 2003, 2006-2009. (Box 22a, Folder 8)
    - Capital Wireless Integrated Network (CapWIN), 2004. (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - 2004 Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments, February 2004. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 2005 Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments, January 2005. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 2006 Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments, February 2006. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 2007 Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments, November 2007. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 2008 Catalog of State and Federal Mandates on Local Governments, November 2008. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Check Point Strikeforce, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Citizen-Soldier Support Council, 2006. (Box 22a, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Commission on Youth Study of Alternative Education Options, 23 April 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 10)
    - Commonwealth Consortium for Mental Health/Criminal Justice Transformation, 2009. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Commonwealth Major IT Project Status Report Dashboard, Baseline Report, 1 July 2002. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Commuting in a State-Owned Vehicle, 2002-2006. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Comprehensive One Stop Workforce Centers MOU, 2008. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Comptroller, Office of the, 2002-2009. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Comptroller, Report of, 30 June 2006. (Box 22a, Folder 11)
    - Comptroller: Popular Report on Virginia Finances for Fiscal Years, 2003, 2004 and 2007. (Box 22a, Folder 12)
    - Comptroller: Quarterly Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance, June 2006-March 2007. (Box 22a, Folder 13)
    - Comptroller: Quarterly Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance, June 2007-March 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 14)
    - Comptroller: Quarterly Report on Statewide Financial Management and Compliance, 30 June 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 15)
    - Congressional Delegation, 2004. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - COOP Plans, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Corrections, Department of, Briefing Book for Governor-Elect Timothy Kaine, November 2005. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Corrections, Department of, Interstate Compact for Adult Offender Supervision, 1 August 2004. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Cost Efficiency, 2003. (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Crime Statistics, 2006. (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Crime Trends, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - CRIMES/LInX Briefing to Secretary of Public Safety, John Marshall, December 2004. (Box 22a, Folder 16)
    - Criminal Justice Services Board, 2002. (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Criminal Sentencing, 2003-2004 and undated. (Box 22a, Folder 17)
    - Virginia Critical Infrastructure Protection and Resiliency Strategic Plan, 8 May 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 18)
    - Deputies Meetings, undated. (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - DHRM, undated. (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Disaster Designation Letters, 2006-2009. (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Disaster Letters, 2007. (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Disaster Letters, 2007-2009. (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Disaster Updates, 2006. (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Disaster Updates, 2006. (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Diversity Fair, 2007. (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - DP-04 Project (Determined Promise), 2004. (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Drug Court, 2002; 2006. (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Drug Offender Screening and Assessment, 2007. (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - DUI Task Force, 2002. (Box 22a, Folder 19)
    - DUI Task Force, 2002-2003. (Box 22a, Folder 20)
    - DUI Task Force, 2003; 2006-2007. (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Election Security Working Group, 2008. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Elko Tract, Public Safety Complex, 1990; 1992. (Box 22a, Folder 21)
    - Emergency Management, Dept. of, 2006-2008. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Emergency Management Accreditation Program (EMAP), 2004. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Executive Agreements, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Executive Orders, 2002-2003. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Executive Orders, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Executive Order 40 - Veterans, 2003. (Box 22a, Folder 22)
    - Implementation of Executive Order 62: Establishing the Commonwealth Consortium for Mental Health/Criminal Justice Transformation, 4 April 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 23)
    - Fairfax County ABC Raid, 2003. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - FBI Intelligence Updates, 2003-2004 (RESTRICTED). (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Filler-Corn, Eileen, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Financial Statements, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Fire Marshall, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Firearm Disposal, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - First 100 Days, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 2004. (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA), 2002-2003. (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Freedom of Information Advisory Council/Joint Commission on Technology and Science, Survey on collection of Social Security Numbers, 15 July 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 24)
    - Follow-Up, 2002-2004. (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Forensics/DNA, 2008. (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Freedmen's Bureau Issue, 2007-2008. (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Gang Report, 2006-2007. (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Gang Violence, 2002-2005. (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Gangs, 2004-2005. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Gemeinschaft House (DOC), 2004. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - General Services, Dept. of, 2002-2004. (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Report of the Governor's Commission on Capital Punishment, Governor George H. Ryan (Illinois), April 2002. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Governor's Counterdrug Support Plan, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Governor's Office for Substance Abuse Prevention (GOSAP) 2007-2008. (Box 22a, Folder 25)
    - Governor's Press Office, 2002. (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Governor's Preventing Crime in Virginia's Minority Communities Task Force Report, 2005. (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Gulf Coast and Atlantic States Regional Task Force, 2006-2007. (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Gubernatorial Incapacity and Succession, 2007. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - HB 113 (2008) Bill Signing, 2008. (Box 22a, Folder 26)
    - HB 5007/SB 5003 Melendez-Diaz Talking Points, 2009. (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Highway Safety, 2006. (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - HJR 159 (2002), 2002. (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - HJR 274 (2004), 2004. (Box 17, Folder 33)